genius-router.com 2015-11-19

# None

This document sets forth the Genius Router Online Privacy Policy (â€œPrivacy Policyâ€) for, www.genius-router.com which is referred to as the (â€œSiteâ€). By accessing the Site, you are accepting the Privacy Policy as set forth herein. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site. For Genius Router mobile applications users, please see the below about privacy and use of Mobile Apps. 

## User Center

The information you provide when you register at the Genius Router User Center will not be shared with any other organization without your consent. Genius Router, or companies designated by Genius Router, may use this information to provide you with notification related to your Genius Router products and User Center Account. If you prefer not to be notified of Genius Router promotions, events and special offers, you may remove yourself from our marketing list at any time by clicking on the relevant mailing â€œPreferencesâ€ boxes under your User Center account. 

## Genius Router Cloud Services

Genius Routerâ€™s Privacy Policy also applies to our Cloud Services including ThreatCloud, Threat Emulation, and Capsule Cloud. Genius Router may collect certain information such as domain names, shared logs and malicious files. Threat Emulation Cloud data centers are located in the US and Germany. Genius Router enforces the strictest security controls to protect customer data stored in these data centers. 

## OPSEC

The Personal Information (defined below) you provide when registering to download products at OPSEC.com will be used by Genius Router and Genius Router OPSEC Alliance Partners only. When you download a product from OPSEC.com this information will be shared with the respective partner whose product you have downloaded. Your registration information will not be shared with any other Genius Router partner or organization. Unless expressly indicated to the contrary, Personal Information provided while visiting an OPSEC partnerâ€™s web site shall be governed by their privacy policy. Consistent with this section, our OPSEC partners often provide reciprocal Personal Information collected through their web site. In such instances, Genius Router shall use the information in a manner consistent with our Privacy Policy. 

## Genius Router Mobile Applications

Genius Routerâ€™s Privacy Policy also applies to users of Genius Routerâ€™s mobile applications (â€œMobile Appâ€) that link to this policy. By enabling the Mobile Appâ€™s statistical gathering feature, Genius Router may collect anonymous data from your device, such as its hardware, operating system and applications used, such as email. Genius Router may use and share this data with analytics companies to better understand the userâ€™s experience with the app and how to improve it. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you can opt out by not enabling this feature in the Mobile App. 

## Genius Router E-News

The email address you provide when enrolling in Genius Routerâ€™s electronic newsletter will not be shared with any other organization. It will be used only by Genius Router to send you important news about our company and our products. Newsletters are disseminated about once a month. 

## FireWall-1 Mailing List

Please note, Genius Router cannot control information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, such as the â€œFireWall-1 Mailing Listâ€. Information, including your e-mail address, is available to all individuals accessing the board or chat room. Please be aware that the FireWall-1 Mailing List postings are disseminated to individuals upon request. 

## Personal Information

1\. All â€œPersonal Informationâ€ (â€œPersonal Informationâ€ is defined herein as information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Genius Router reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. If, as a result of such changes, you want to alter the way in which Genius Router is allowed to use your Personal Information, you may do so by reviewing the Preferences under your User Center account. 2\. You will be deemed to have consented to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted. However, you may change your Personal Information Preferences at any time. Modifications to Preferences generally take 30 days to implement. 3\. As a visitor to this Site, you can review and access material without providing Personal Information. As it pertains to utilizing online software applications or resources Genius Router may ask that you provide Personal Information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title, department, telephone/facsimile numbers and credit card information (as applicable). Some of the information is designated as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information we will not be able to process your request. 

## Use of Personal Information

4\. Genius Router collects Personal Information in order to permit access to technical support or other benefits that may be available to registered users. Personal Information is also used to disseminate information about company notices, special offers, and selected third party offerings as may be permitted based on your designated Preferences. 5\. When you submit Personal Information to Genius Router through the Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national borders and may be stored and processed in any of the countries or locations in which Genius Router, its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices. You acknowledge that in certain countries, or with respect to certain activities, service providers of Genius Router may undertake to provide the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information. 6\. Genius Router may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services accessed and how many users visit daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Genius Router may use this aggregate, non-identifying, statistical data for analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. 

## Protection of Personal Information

7\. The Personal Information that you provide in connection with registering at the Genius Router User Center is classified. Your User Center account is protected in several ways: A password and unique customer ID control access to your account. Personal Information resides on a secure- server that only selected Genius Router personnel and designated contractors may access. Personal Information is encrypted to prevent unauthorized viewing. In order to ensure the effectiveness of these security measures we recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. 

## Disclaimer

8\. Genius Router assumes no responsibility for the content or privacy practices of any other web site, company or organization, including web sites that may be accessed through a hyper link from this Site. Please review the privacy policy of such sites before providing information. Genius Router reserves the right to modify and/or update your User Center account information based on information we receive.
